hello sir
why are you all standing outside
you should log in
he was in a hurry
he just did it impulsively
this doesn't look like him
he took the hard drive
no weapon found
not even one hair left
he was telling
how we used to go to the beach together
he said
that I was happy then
you remember this too
no
I guess
what is that woman
it's you
and that boy is minjae
that boy next to me
is it you minjae
looked at us from here
he was jealous of you
and wanted me to
took care of him
bro i gotta see choi soon
don't forget to thank me later
she's already on her way to my studio
you better hurry up
good until the very end
he tried to help me
this criminal will call again
we have to catch this scoundrel
please help me
I'll think
how are you
I will act
as if I am you
i will think like jung and shin
and act like jeon and shin
please help me catch him
Unsan serial murder case
case materials number 1
아아
아
autopsy report
Crime scene of the victim Song Biyeong Chul
으으으으아하하하하하
came
long time no see
it's already very late
I was urgently called for a check
this dead guy won't go anywhere anyway
God acknowledge the help from that
who was thought dead
it's already hard enough
when will they find out about Suyolya
it will be almost impossible to contain the consequences
yes senpyo
commissioner
will take the blame
that was the condition
the price of tires offered in exchange for consultation on the case is not
it was worth agreeing
even now I still don't know
Am I doing the right thing?
I ruined everything
yesterday a man about 40 years old
family breadwinner
hanged himself in the house
which became a trap for him for real estate scammers
the note was not found
they even did an autopsy
after all
Of course they found the note
and in it he only apologized
begging for forgiveness again and again
but he’s not to blame for anything, right?
but all I could write in the autopsy report
this is death by hanging
just 3 words
if I were allowed to write
what I feel in this report
I mean that
Don't let your emotions get in the way of your work
if you give them free rein
everything will only get more complicated
while you're here, hug the kids
consciously and warmly
sure have a nice journey bye
and the juice is ready
you know what to do and it’s not time
as long as possible
you can't upset him in any way
unidentified number
gotta take on the challenge
hello who's calling
it's like I don't know
webtoon author
it was you
of course, who else?
understandable
everything looked too careless
that wasn't our style
just a bunch of mirrors and terribly sloppy paint job
left a bold signature in a visible place
it was quite a sight
all this talk about the final scene
it was just chatter
what is she doing
How is this scene not the final one?
he died painting a scene
this was his final scene
oh I haven't laughed seriously in so long
god you want to remind everyone of my heritage
you
I would never do that
you're just a pathetic parody
what was that
captain cha
그렇지
hi
so intrusive
you will still envy me what is this
I became interested
guess you're in jail
I'm free, you can't, but I can
Canyon Hoys houses for miners
burned with a hot spoon and broke all 4 limbs before
how he died of blood loss
true 4
to be honest
I was a little hasty this time
I do not deny my deepest apologies
it was spontaneous
but the next one is for real
I'll try to hang up again very soon, sorry
you prepared the spoon this is important
I have everything
even a hand torch
excellent
almost like we're doing it together
I feel it too
you know the order
very good
are you sure that this woman is helping us now?
what who is this about
he came see you
chan check the records and find this place
when we get there
let's take the security room
code and parking
view
building visit log for the last 30 minutes and check
isn't someone coming?
whose did you hear yes
let's go
This is Paesongyu Major Crimes Department
requesting support
I found the juice
second esta prime minister wanted
esta premier wanted
esta premier wanted in yunhudong thank you
ok hurry up eat
captain cha
only a fool expects to catch him without blood
special forces are on their way
should arrive within 10 minutes
Chan will stay and log into the hotel Internet
she'll look at their CCTV footage.
we're on our way
tell chan from tires to take so long
as much as possible
captain cha asked to buy some time
be patient and let him wake up from the anesthesia
you know my style
I didn't use anything
he likes to be tied up
he even brought his stockings
it's not interesting
if it's too easy
today's equipment includes a hammer
made in korea
you need to calm down
calm down already
we're just getting started
what are you so afraid of
police let me in
we are connected to the hotel's video surveillance system
where is this room
This is a studio suite type room, there are 57 of them
what floors are from 3 to 13th
from 3 to 13 you can say
which ones are busy now
Misty Knight performing nearby
group booking
we are fully loaded
everyone registered 30 minutes ago
most should be in their rooms by now
by employee pairs
juice from 13th down
sunggyu lead the group well
me and detective kim
let's start with 3, block off all possible escape routes, captain
the victim is already in danger
let's first block the exits and sound the alarm
first you need to save the victim
we just started searching from the 3rd and 13th floors
What if he hears the alarm and runs away from another floor?
we can't risk it
need to catch him
quickly
numbers 13 zero 5 zero 4 12 17
20 and 22 check everyone has gone
numbers 304 5
12/17 to 20 and 22
ahead there is sir
sorry we are from the police
I'm sorry, I'm from the police
sorry have a nice day
police excuse me
sorry we are from the police
we are from the police
excuse me for a moment
thank you
this is a workout
what to watch next
his arms or legs
neck too fast true
chan are you done with the cameras?
Yes, none of the guests are listed as subscribers
Chewie main event of the day spoon
and a flashlight in a duet wait
and today the mirrors are just for you
I will honestly repeat your style
no need to do this
I know the police are with you
if you try to stall for time or arrange something else
oh don't be absurd
ok this is my favorite part
ㅎㅎ
all possible escape routes are blocked
captain the escape route is blocked
let's sound the alarm
captain cha he acts the same as the killer 23 years ago
captain cha if we sound the alarm
he will understand and run away
even if he runs away
we'll catch all the waste routes are blocked
until he jumps off the roof
we can catch him
even if he's on a different floor
he will die like this
you can't do without blood
if we want to catch the criminal okay
and what does that mean
stop
just stop for a minute
you have to think
like him like me junho
captain, the cameras on the 4th floor were turned off 2 hours ago
room 400 18 what
this room 400 18
block all entrances to the 4th floor
아
this is the final captain
what happened what the
don't crowd, stay calm
clear the passage
we are from the police
suspect babe guests
press yourself against the walls
please police
please press yourself against the walls come on in
press yourself against the walls
clear the passage
we pass carefully
call an ambulance urgently
Mister Mister
can you hear me I'm from the police
sir
sir it's already over
don't worry
show yourself
oh captain cha
o
sir are you okay there
he ran away because we thought
that the victim will be a guest
fortunately the victim is still alive
good job
아우 아우
but this is captain cha
turned on the alarm
wow look
how quickly he reacted it was me
he didn't want to he thought
that the criminal will escape
what did he say
that catching him will come with blood
what happened to him
pakminge what
minjae you can't die
wake up you should wake up minjae
I will think like Jonashin and act like Jonashin
please help us catch him
sungyu
you can dig something up on captain cha
captain cha yes
try to find out
why was he suddenly transferred to us from the narcotics department
and why him
find out what kind of relationship he has with Park Min Jae
and why has he changed so much lately?
why are you late again sorry
taking into account the condition of your son and his age, custody
most likely you will get it
his mother is fine
but still be careful
a guardianship specialist will be present
I'm sorry
hello frog hind legs
frog hind legs
hujeong can you tell
how many people live in your home
these people are here now
wow what a great drawing
you drew this hujun
who is this
and then who is it
wow good job
where's your mom
ahh
so this is your mom
please ask him
who is he happier with?
with mom or dad
thank you wait
this was not in the package
even though he's already worried enough
there will be such a question
but we have to ask
maybe we can end this
Hojoong is so upset
you can ask him
dear madam
please ask him
you almost got him
he almost killed a man
the victim is still alive
you probably don't care
it was in yunpo
remember
the three of us
including myeonjae
spent the whole day on the beach
I added ninja to the picture
I remember the beach
he would like it
this was filmed at a crime scene in a hotel
and this is a case of 4 murders
which you committed 23 years ago
he tried to repeat this murder
compare 2 cases and say
if you find anything
I can't go back there
do with it what you want
you know this song
yes
he even sang the same song
what am I 23 years ago
where did he know about this?
this was not in your confession either
he was there
that's right
he was there he watched you at the crime scene
then why did he
then he didn’t report it to the police
because I
fulfilled his wish
I didn’t make these 2 living storages
they were 1.5 centimeters wide
these were shallow wounds
they could have been inflicted by a small knife
for example stationery
this is the best he could do
even with full strength
he must have been hiding in the closet or something
after I left
his anger probably made him give the corpse more blows
the victim had a wife and small son
only 2 family members
if these were shallow wounds remember that
mining town
there was a boy there
who always walked 1
mom
that boy carried around a dead cat as a toy
his whole body was covered in various wounds
1 side of his nose was even deformed
due to a terrible burn
kang yeon ho
he locked
son in the bathroom and forced to eat human feces
the boy was shackled to his feet
after all
he couldn't even stand his breath
so he heated a spoon on the fire and put it to the boy’s nose
how could he do this to his son?
your father tried to kill you too
when he was 12 years old
his name is canyon john
that boy must be
saw me at the crime scene
in the eyes of this boy
I was the one who fulfilled his long-standing wish
no wonder
that I interested him
it's obvious
and brought him to you
and your family
to your home
to johnny
Chief Choe
I need security right now
for junyoung yes
it looks like the criminal was even humming the same tune
like scientist shin
at the crime scene 23 years ago
the fact that he knew about it means
that he witnessed her crime
he could even be hiding nearby
canyon xo her victim had a son 23 years ago
the violence this boy suffered
it was so terrible
that some media outlets even defended Chen and Shin
This is Canyon June his son
Looks like he's the real culprit in this case
this is his registration card but
this is the only record about him
which I could find
his mother was hospitalized in a nursing home
due to dementia
caused by alcohol around this time
but after that he didn’t even have a change of address
he has no bank accounts
no credit cards
looks like he hired someone
so that he gives him a new identity
even I wouldn't use it
this is the name of his life with this name
there must have been a hell on earth
do you have the address of his mother's nursing home
San Bonya is nearby
send me the address
you two can interrogate your acquaintances
the victims went well
right that's why
he doesn't care about human lives at all
he only cares about recognition
why do we catch criminals
we are trying to prevent new victims
did you even ask him
what did you ask captain acha
did he do it for recognition?
or just tried to do everything
so that there are no new victims
I the criminal managed to escape
what are you talking about
here he is
aren't we 1 team
anyway
digging through your partner's dirty laundry
I'll do what you want
do whatever you want
this guy is thinking
how can you disrespect me so much hey okay
I'll do everything myself
yeah that's right kang yeonjun
have you seen your son recently
yeonjun
my son
he needs to run
why canyon june should be escaped
madam
uh captain
can I talk to you for a minute
you remember something
we believe the victim met her
do you see he is a close friend
your friend is in intensive care
because of this criminal we must catch the culprit
you can tell everything
that you remember everything is fine
to be honest he has a bit of a nasty side
he was subscribed to different applications
and went to different women
yes to her too
look he kept repeating it
so in awe of this girl
and then just silence
I'm also a man
naturally interesting
I bought him a couple of glasses of wine and started asking him
then he told the truth
he's in big trouble
by and large yes
in what sense is the face
said beautiful things
but the photos on her profile were definitely fake
but it seems
that's ok
Most people on this app don't have real profile photos.
but the real problem was
just absurd
wait, can you tell me this?
why not we are the police
relax captain
repeat after me
where are frog hind legs from?
just try frog hind legs smile at the paws
frog hind legs paws paws
like she looks more at people's facial expressions
than their words
that's the thing
frog hind legs true
this psycho met women here secretly at work
and whose yes
tea asked him to turn off all the lights
as soon as we entered
then he felt uneasy
but he didn't want to look like a weakling
so I let her
and then she threatened or intimidated him
on the contrary on the contrary
yes during the act
she suddenly asked to choke her
true yes
he thought she just had perverted taste
and just pretended
but she screamed stronger than her soul, stronger
she egged him on more and more
then he got scared
what could harm her
and stopped
after that he found an excuse and ran away
anything else
what else
what scared him the most
when he choked her
she flew into a frenzy and asked him
just kill her
she said if he does it
it will save many people
isn't this creepy
so he stopped
madam
you see
I'm asking because I'm very curious
can you tell me
why does yeonjun have to run
he killed dollar
can you tell
who is further
dog
neighbor's dog
looks like a puppy
she's a little confused
madam
yeonjun
you saw him recently
when
just now
what
he came down again
to become a girl
he put on makeup again
he needs to run my husband is coming
sorry by accident
she already had another visitor before us
yes she left with confidence
how did you come
yes detective kim
they have a visitor log
but their CCTV cameras are broken
according to the nurse and receptionists
she was wearing a hoodie and a mask
but it was definitely a woman
woman
yes
nothing to report
good
good job
she said June Canyon was there
due to severe dementia
it's difficult to interrogate her
Well, even if Kang Nyeonjun really was there
this is impossible to confirm
I thought about it
mother canyon juna
not always in your right mind
but everything she said could be true
what do you mean
she claims
that he was her son
that he was carrying a dead cat or dog with him
and that he was wearing makeup
if all this is true
I'm not sure
Was this somehow connected with my father’s bullying?
or he has long had gender dysphoria
but what am I sure of
so this is
that Kang Young Joon had antisocial tendencies since childhood
he could have gender dysphoria
as a reaction to a traumatic childhood
if that's the case now
after 23 years
June Canyon appearance
be completely different
he could even make the transition
that is, you think
that the woman who visited the nursing home
maybe the canyon is June
also known as chuy
come on, this is too much
you said it yourself
June Canyon's childhood was no different from hell on earth
considering this is a response to trauma June Canyon
there could be a complete creation of a new personality
the injury was so bad
that rebirth as a new person
became the only means of survival
I'm looking for a clinic where psychiatric treatment is not required
or Gender Dysphoria Certificate
damn
we suspect
what could this man do
plastic surgery and now looks like someone
in these photos
have you seen someone like that
for 1 of these persons
thank you for meeting me
gender confirmation surgery
usually a long and complex process
rather, even after confirming the diagnosis, code f 64 zero
at the psychiatrist
you need to undergo hormonal therapy from 6 months to a year
so you should have too
yes I had surgery in Thailand
maybe you recognize her
no I don't know
after all
I'm not friends with all the transgender women in the world.
Looks like she went abroad
to make the operation easier
the operation may have a number of possible complications
and long-term care is required after it
after returning
she was supposed to see a doctor for post-op
care
sir here is the list of clinics
let's see the clinics
specializing in gender affirming surgeries
Lubinous Plastic Surgery Clinic
he gave me a special ride
pak mincha suspect in the case
and his screams are minchey
prove that they had a close relationship
and now his dear friend has been killed
well
the world is full of wannabes
just look at these pictures
here
I'm not sure it would be difficult to know someone that's why
thanks for your cooperation
then maybe
except for these photos
were there any patients
which seemed a little unusual
sorry detective
yes
I used to work in another clinic
and you met her there
yes this clinic was known in the community
and many of her patients were members of the community
unsuccessful surgery abroad
can even lead to pelvic necrosis
I also saw a lot of seriously ill patients
but even with the risk of death they still go for the operation
some told me
that all their lives they lived with a female soul in a male body
this was their path to happiness
what about her
that kid
was different from others
Of course she was also happy to have a body
which reflected
who she really was
but I also heard
as she muttered something to herself
this is such an advantage
that society does not perceive women as a threat
what
you heard I think
she's a criminal
I found a clinic and a doctor
where that nurse worked
hard to believe
that she even went to the extent of gender reassignment to simplify the murder
but I'm sure she really took advantage of this chance
this is our criminal
according to the nurse
the clinic is closed
how do we find a doctor
let's catch the criminal
what happened
something happened, you guys
and pakminge
pakminge
unfold unfold
who is this child
you said you weren't hiding anything anymore
Mr. Chasuyeol
please leave our team
let's ask around and find this doctor
then we will catch the criminal
Jeon Yi Shin also asked you to do this
yes yes this is a woman
really
my mom and what
so what?
worried
that this could negatively impact the investigation
so these are your thoughts
yes
please leave
what exactly didn’t work out because of me
I think she wanted you in exchange for a consultation
but after catching the criminal
we don't need her anymore
it means I'm useless to you
inspector hour ul
you swore that you would no longer hide anything from us
we don't need a captain
who deceives his own team even more so
if he doesn't care about the lives of the victims and that
seohyunho
would be dead
if we had waited just one more second
so now he's dead
you lied to us all, bastard
we refuse
follow his orders
we can't do it anymore
choose sir
who do you want on our team or his team?
sir we are very close
now we can catch the criminal
just passed away
suyeol if you follow him
we will decide that you want him on your team
Suyul should be at home
want to be 1
전혀
do you remember
the story that menja told you
about
serial killer
who lived in our city
when we were little
bagamula
killer mantis series
this is my mom
Mrs. Li Chunyun
Jung Yi Shin was arrested
when I was 11 years old
she was arrested for brutal murder
at least 5 men
and after 23 years I met her again
Mr. Jeon
my maternal grandfather
even changed my name
set up a fake grave in yonpo
as if his daughter had died
and tried to forget everything and
I need some time
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to shock you so much
It's natural that you're shocked
someone who killed
five are missing
serial killer
who killed six
your husband's mother
it's a shock, it's scary, it's understandable
I know
I
you know but that's a but
she was here after all
I didn't know she was so disgusting
yeah disgusting
and I consider myself disgusting
I didn't want to say about you
then why did you leave me
no you got it all wrong
it's not that normal
I understand
just me
it's just too much to understand at once
no sorry
I didn't mean that
jeongyeon I know
you want a child soyul but
the thing is
I'm afraid of myself
this feeling
that blood is the black tires of that monster
that he gave birth to me
flows in my veins
this is cruel
nasty scary
disgusting blood
after I became a policeman
every time I saw a brutal murder scene
every time I pulled out a gun
to catch the criminal
every time I was covered in blood
I had a thought
am I really
I enjoy the smell of blood
maybe I don't care about catching criminals
maybe I just want to legally shoot someone
that's what came to my mind
I don't want it to be blood
about which you know nothing
moved on
what are you even talking about sooyeol
no suyeol
I love you jeongyeon
I'm sorry for lying to you
아
the criminal is now agitated
she's trying to cover her tracks
bring me to me
I'm fussing right now
he is also desperate
like you, what if this is not a mother's story
who helps her son
what if it's the mother
using her son with evil intentions
she said that you were happy because of her
how did you meet chunion
dispatch all available units in the area
chunion will come here
this is a special order from the commissioner
we continue to work independently
if you go there
you're going to die I have to do it